<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<feedback>
	<quote>
		<text>If there was no MyBB, I'd rather not have a forum as everything else isn't as powerful or as easy to customize.</text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://gamesrule.mihopa.com/">GameZRule</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[The support team is really great, they are very nice when helping out users.]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[Jake]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[The very best in forum software.  Excellent design and features make MyBB a winner!]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.webdevote.com/">kodaks</a>]]></author>
	</quote>	
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[I saw MyBB, installed it, tried it, loved it! Others feel the same way, as I know because I've convinced them to change over. It is just as powerful as the competitors, even the ones you have to pay for, and definitely the most powerful and professional FREE forum software out there today. I tried MyBB, why don't you?]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.rctgo.com/">Belloman</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[I tried many boards for my company, but really the only one that did what would be best for my users and staff was MyBB. It really is a wonderful board.]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.louhabs.com/">Lou Habs</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[The support from the mybb makers is wonderful. After a problem with my board, Chris Boulton himself came onto my board and helped me fix my problem, and ensure it never happened again. Shortly after, he released a fix to make sure everyone using the board, had the fix. They fix every bug they find, and really put their heart into the project. That is why, I support and recommend, MyBB.]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.louhabs.com/">Louhabs</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[I have tried every other software and I was a huge fan of IPB until their switch. MyBB has given me back everything IPB had and even more!]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://webdapper.com/GrossGateway/">Chris</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[Provided a perfect platform on which to build our community-website. Easy-to-use interfaces, flexibility of the system, timely security-updates and ultimate flexibility in regards to customization has made it a breeze to build viable professional web site with a funding of a non-profit! Brilliant package!]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[Kimmo]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[With MyBB, I was able to set up a great free forum effortlessly within minutes! My forum has since then grown into a fairly large webmaster community. Thanks MyBB, for giving me my life back!]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.webmaster-corner.com/">EGS</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[I looked on the web for different forums, first was IPB, because I used it at another forum, but got sticker shock when I looked at the price. Then, I found phpBB, but it looked too "basic" for my site. And then I found MyBB, it look professional, was easy to customize, and is very secure. ]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.coolestech.com/">Cool_Guy</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
	<quote>
		<text><![CDATA[After being disappointed by other forums software for years I decided to try Mybb.   Immediately I was taken by it's easy install, quick learning curve, and excellent overall function. Thank you Mybb for creating a top-notch free forum software that rivals even paid ones.]]></text>
		<author><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.democracyforums.com/">Jesse Labrocca</a>]]></author>
	</quote>
</feedback>